question_data = [
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "The Lego Group was founded in 1932.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Bulls are attracted to the color red.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "The Sun rises from the North.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Is a dog a mammal?",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Scotland voted to become an independent country during the referendum from September 2014.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Gumbo is a stew that originated in Louisiana.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "The Great Wall of China is visible from the moon.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "&quot;27 Club&quot; is a term used to refer to a list of famous actors, musicians, and artists who died at the age of 27.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Ping-Pong originated in England",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Romanian belongs to the Romance language family, shared with French, Spanish, Portuguese and Italian. ",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    }
  ]